Finding Aid for the Carey McWilliams Papers LSC.1319
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 9. Publicity and criticism, 1929-1980; 1.5 boxes
  - Assorted publicity materials, 1976-1978; 34 items. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Assorted printed materials, including clippings, letters, programs, newsletters, and McWilliams's resume. Many of these materials refer to his lecture appearances and honors.
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1976-1978; ca. 30 items. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Newspaper clippings. Also includes copies of the publications California Historical Courier and ACLU News.
  - Reviews of The Education of Carey McWilliams, 1979; ca. 40 items. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Clippings and photocopies of reviews.
  - Assorted publicity materials, 1979-1980; 31 items. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Assorted printed materials, including clippings, letters, leaflets, and copies of Quill and Somos. Many of these materials refer to his lecture appearances and honors.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1980; ca. 20 items. (Box 91, Folder 6)